Inventory of the Overseas Weekly photographs
Hoover Institution Archives
- Contact Sheet 16332, 1970 May 23
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pfc. Richard Hotchkiss - S. Sgt. Walter J. Massey - shooting - segregation - Jay Ninh shooting May 23, 1970.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pacific - May 23 - ID for Tay Ninh shooting story - Frames 4-10: Bleachers where shooting occurred. In frames 4-6, piles of dirt used to cover blood can be seen. Frames 14-16: Pfc Richard Hotchkiss, quoted in the story. Frames 17-20: S Sgt Walter J. Massey, NCOIC of standdown center, quoted in story.
- Contact Sheet 16333, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pacifik - ID sheet #1 for Cambodia special report - May 11, 1970 - Frames 4a-13 show trails used to infiltrate supplies from Cambodia into Nam. 14, 15: Aerial view of Cambodian village. Rest of roll is 105mm howitzer crew at LZ Evans.
- Contact Sheet 16334, 1970 May 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas Pazifik - ID sheet #7 for Cambodia - May 11, 70 - Frames 4-7 show 1st Cav GIs working on their .50 cal Machine guns at LZ Evans. Rest of roll shows guys throwing empty ammo cases on truck, 105's firing and more stacks of weapons, plus a mug shot of two GIs.
- Contact Sheet 16335, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - vehicles.
- Contact Sheet 16336, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas Pazifik - ID sheet #5 for Cambodia - May 11, 70 - Frames 1-9 show 1st Cav Div. GIs from recon platoon at work in cache site. 10, 11 Chinook tries to recover it's mate that was downed by engine failure. Rest of roll is recon platoon and their stacks of captured booty.
- Contact Sheet 16337, 1970 May 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - no. 15.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet # 2 for Cambodia report - May 11, 70 - Frames 3-5 show 105mm howitzer working out at LZ Evans. 6, 7: Soul brothers at LZ Evans. 8-10: Weary grunt takes a break. 12: Chinook comes into LZ. 12: Guys move out. 14-17A: GIs from 1st Cav Div. go skinny dipping in a Cambodian Creek at LZ Evans. 20, 21: GI hooks up supplies to Chinook helicopter for drop-off in Cambodia. 25A, 26: More shots of GI booking Cambodia-bound cargo to belly-hook of chinook chopper. Rest of roll is a NDP (night defensive position) of 11th Armored Cav Regt.
- Contact Sheet 16338, 1970 May 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Cambodia - ID sheet #4 - May 11, 70 - Frames 3a-8a: Show friendly villagers near LZ Evans, Cambodia. Rest of roll is guys stacking captured weapons, grunts patrolling through Cache sites. Note GIs going through captured gear in the last two frames of roll.
- Contact Sheet 16339, 1970 May 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - weapons (captured).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #6 for Cambodia - May 11, 70 - Frames 3, 4: Guy on ground is heat casualty. 5-9: Shows 1st Cav Div. grunts burning empty rifle boxes captured in Cambodia. 10: GI walks away from burning boxes. 11: Routine patrol. 12-19: Shows recon platoon loading captured rifles on chopper. 20: Mox nix shots of artillery at LZ Evans.
- Contact Sheet 16340, 1970 May 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia no. 1 - Cambodia.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #14 for Cambodia--APC patrol - May 11, 70 - Frames 3a-25a show faces of 11th ACR GIs as the patrol meanders down Hwy 13. 26, 27: Your intrepid photog, Don Hirst. Rest of roll is more faces. Note: The last frame on the continuation of the contact sheet that is circled in blue shows APC hitting a mine. That's where the smoke comes from. Use this one please…
- Contact Sheet 16341, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia.
- Contact Sheet 16342, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas Pazifik - ID sheet #8 for Cambodia - May 11, 70 - All shots are aerial views of 11th Armored Cav Regt NDP.
- Contact Sheet 16343, 1970 May 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - not printed.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas Pazifik - ID sheet #10 for Cambodia -- For APC Patrol - May 11, 7 - Frame 4: Milestone announces 4 klicks to frontier. 5: APC moving down road. 6, 7: 11th ACR GI wounded by mine clutches medevac tag. 8-13: Wounded being medevaced. 14, 15: APC moves past one damaged by mine. 16, 17: Combat engineer with can of coke in hand walks down road. 22-24: Deserted customs house just inside Cambodian boarder. 25, 26: Engineer carries mine he just rmoved from road. 27: The Sheridian that hit a mine. Rest of roll: Sign announces Cambodian Police post ahead--armor in background.
- Contact Sheet 16344, 1970 May 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #11 for Cambodia -- APC patrol - May 11, 70 - Whole roll is general shots of 11th ACR NDP near Snuol. There are several pix of Cambodian kids and old people that might be interesting.
- Contact Sheet 16345, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - Cambodia no.12 - partially scan (MGD).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #12 for Cambodia -- APC patrol - May 11, 70 - Frame 4 shows medic rushing to aid of wounded guys on APC that just hit a mine. Milestone says it's 4 klicks to the border--frame 5 is same thing. Rest of roll up to frame 34 shows the wounded being treated. Note the .50 cal lying on the ground in most of the pix--it was blown right off the track by the force of the blast. Last three on roll of your own intrepid (and rather scared at the time) photographer.
- Contact Sheet 16346, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - Cambodia no. 13.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID shet #13 for Cambodia--APC patrol - May 11, 70 - Frames 3-5 show medevac of three GIs wounded by mine. 6: The APC being pushed off road. 7, 8: Faces of 11th ACR GIs. 9, 10: Trails alongside the road used for infiltration. 11: GI sips water. 12: Smoke is from Sheridan that hit a mine. Rest of roll shows damaged Sheridan.
- Contact Sheet 16347, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #3 for Cambodia report - May 11, 70 - Frames 6-8: General shots of LZ Evans, Cambodia. 9-16: GIs (1st Cav Div) take a break and go skinny dipping at LZ Evans (note some of them giving peace sign). Rest of roll is sequence of GI who was hit by failing tree being medevaced at LZ Evans. Ignore frame 32--it's John Saar, Life Magazine.
- Contact Sheet 16348, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - No.1 - boxing - John Bailey - Frank Espiritu.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #1 for boxing - April 2, 70 - Hirst - Frames 4-26: Guy in white shirt and trunks is John Bailey, Navy. Guy in dark is Abraham Langit. I shot the first two strips under available light, hence the darkness. 27-36A: White shirt and trunks is Frank Espiritu, Navy. Guy in dark outfit is Ding Macalalad.
- Contact Sheet 16349, 1970 June 6
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Guam - instamatic film.
- Contact Sheet 16350, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - helicopters - air strikes - partially scan (MGD).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: ARVN 9th Division troops Heli Assault on outlaw ships - selection of frames - Frames 5, 6: En route to LZ. Frame 7: Troops alight and one soldier sinks down a creek. Frame 8: He pulls himself out of creek; soldiers running for cover. Frame 9: Troops on LZ. 175th Outlaws: Selection of frames showing operations with ARVN troops in the Mekong Delta. - Frame 12: Door gunner firing on approach to LZ, ARVN soldier winces at deafening noise. Frame 13: Another door gunner and ARVN. Frames 14, 15, 16: ARVN troops aboard helo -- these are RF/PF troops who, with a platoon of police field-force went on a search and clear op. Their conduct in embarking and debarking was better than most of the … Frame 17: First taste of flying - RF/PF troops on an operation near Cau Hang, Vinh Binh Province.
- Contact Sheet 16351, 1970 May 28
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - plane crash (Cunningham) - S. Sgt. Marvin R. Norton - Sgt. David Steffen - Pfc. Mark Lindholm - burning plane.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Caption sheet for unsouped roll of tri-x - May 28, 70 - Hirst - It contains, in the following order: Several shots of a burning plane being hosed down by firemen. Slug it: "Brig Gen Hubert S. Cunningham narrowly escaped death when the U21 he and his staff were riding in crashed and burned at LZ English. No one was injured in the crash, caused by a collapsed landing gear, and the popular honche is gung-ho … Brig rode away from his narow brush with the grim reaper, he was heard to say, "Airborne!" Next several pix of S Sgt Norton, quote in story about mysterious Caucasian and subject of story on recon. Norton is in fatigues with camoflaged face, etc. Next are several pix of (left-right) Sgt David Steffen, Pfc Mark Lindholm, both quotes in mysterious Caucasian story. Last two or three shots are the same with Norton in the middle.
- Contact Sheet 16406, 1970 May 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - recreation camp Alpha - Lisa Cronin - May 11, 1970.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pacific - May 11 - Camp Alpha - Frames 3-4-5-6: Entrance to Camp Alpha, the processing center for GIs going on R&R. Frames 7-8-9: Soldiers waiting to get processed through Alpha. Frame 10: Soldiers wait outside Robinson Hall. Named after a construction chief who died on the job, the hall is Alpha's main processing terminal. Frame 11: Alpha's check-in workers wait for GIs to come through. Frame 12: Alpha's new mess hall under construction. Frame 13: Another shot of the mess hall. Frame 14-15: GIs are checked in on their way to Hong Kong. Frame 16-17: GIs are putting their luggage on Alpha's racks on the way out. Frame 18: A group of soldiers on their way to Hong Kong wait for a briefing. Frame 20: Australian soldiers are checked by customs specialists.
- Contact Sheet 16407, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Korea.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Oseas pacifik - People / with art - Proctor - May 28 - Art identification - Negs six, seven, and eight are Kim Ho Kyoon and friend.
- Contact Sheet 16408, 1970 May 14
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - "A" - Navy - Navy guns - May 14, 1970.
- Contact Sheet 16409, 1970 May 14
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - "B" - Navy - Navy guns.
- Contact Sheet 16410, 1970 June 20
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy D - planes - carrier ranger - Vung Tau R & R.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Oseas pacifik - Targets and men / with art - Picture identification sheet D - 1 is the skipper of the destroyer USS Brinkley Bass on the bridge; 2 thru 4 are general shots at the China beach, Danang, R&R center (Vung Tau R&R Center story). The aircraft carrier series started at five to the end of the sheet. Most of the shots are self explanatory except, perhaps, for 10. This is a hernia operation in the operating theater of the USS Ranger. E Sheet: Frames one thru five are pix of the guys involved in Project Reach on the Ranger (see men story) are general pictures of flight operations. F Sheet: General shots of flight operations except for frame 23, which is another shot of the hernia operation.
- Contact Sheet 16411, 1970 May 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy E - carrier ranger - fight operations - Project R.
- Contact Sheet 16412, 1970 May 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - F - Navy - carrier ranger - flight operations.
- Contact Sheet 16414, 1970 June 20
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sgt. Richard Merlin - Pfc. Sonny Robertson - Capt. James Hergen - Pvt. Kenneth Henry - Capt. Benjamin Fishburne shooting - Pvt. Edward Hall - trials - Chu Lai.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Picture identifications for Chu Lai trials - Frame 1: Pvt Kenneth Henry. Frame 2-3: Defense Lawyer Capt. Benjamin Fishburne with Pvt. Kenneth Henry. Frame 4, 5, 6, 7: Sgt. Richard A. Merlin, the MP Robinson. Frame 10: Pfc. Sonny Robinson leaves the courtroom. Frame 11, 12: Pfc Sonny Robinson with defense lawyer Capt. James Hergen. Frame 13, 14, 15: Pvt. Edward Hall.
- Contact Sheet 16415, 1970 July 4
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Lance Cpl. Andrew M. Harris - Reuben A. Garland - Capt. George H. O'Kelley - bombs and explosives - acquittal - laundry - strike.
- Contact Sheet 16416, 1970 April 4
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - No. 2 - boxing. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #2 for boxing match - April 4, 70 - Hirst - Frames 3-7: Amada Manla (Navy) in dark trunks, white shirt. Boy Langit is in dark shirt, white trunks. 10-14: Jacob Melton (Navy) in dark trunks, light shirt gets a beating from Alex Alhambra. 15-18a: Roger Henry (Navy), white shirt, dark trunks, trounces Rudy Alhambra (dark trunks and shirt). 19-21: Rudy Serrato (Navy) white shirt and trunks, wipes Arthur Prado. 22-24: Navy's Lance Gumbert in dark shots and light shirt defeats Romeo Yulo, dark shorts and dark shirt. 25-rest of roll: Navyman Joe Reynolds (dark shirt, shorts and headguard) trounced Butch Miguel (plain t-shirt, dark shorts).
- Contact Sheet 16417, 1970 June 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - Sp4 James H. Driverr - murder trial - Don Hrist - June / 11 / 1970.
- Contact Sheet 16418, 1970 June 9
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - air missions - Vietnamese - Vietnamese pilots - no. 1.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #1 for story on Vietnamese pilots - June 9, 70 - Hirst - All pix are of F5s in flight. Frame 8a shows F3 dropping bomb.
- Contact Sheet 16419, 1970
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - air missions - Vietnamese - Vietnamese pilots no.2.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet #2 for story on Vietnamese pilots - … 9, 70 - All pix are of F5s in flight.
- Contact Sheet 16420, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pvt. Michael A. Schwartz - Pfc. Tomas R. Boyd Jr. - Howard P. Trockman (lawyer) - crimes - acquittal. NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pacific - June 25 - ID for pictures for Boyd trial - Frames 2 & 3: Marine in hat, sunglasses, smoking cigarettes, face toward camera is Pvt. Michael A. Schwartz. Frames 16 through 19: Pfc Thomas R. Boyd Jr. with defense lawyer Howard P. Trockman, in civilian clothes.
- Contact Sheet 16421, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pvt. Michael A. Schwartz - crimes.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pacific - June 22 - ID for undeveloped roll of film - for Scwarz trial - Scwarz is only man who appears in each frame. He is white, smoking a cigarette, and in a few frames is near a vehicle. The photos are by Lisa Cronin, who says there's a small chance she's mixed up rolls of film. If this roll doesn't fit above descriptions, please return negatives to us ASAP.
- Contact Sheet 16423, 1970 June 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - visitors - VIP visit to Shakey's Hill.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Oseas pacifik - VIPs art IDs- June 11 - Proctor - ART IDs for VIP story, Shakey's Hill - Negs 8 to 11: First frames of a single Negro GI drinking milk, last shot is same guy with another Brother, also drinking milk, and wearing NVA battle bowler. Negs 12 and 13: A cache being blown up near the base. Negs 14 and 15: A GI barber at work. Neg 20: Inspecting a lean-to hut, rather the remains of one, near Shakey. Negs 21 to 23: A captured ox cart and cycle in front of a sign that reads "Welcome to Shakey's Hill." Neg 25: An aerial view of Shakey's.
- Contact Sheet 16424, 1970 June 15
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - "A" operations negatives - Cambodian operations - partial scan (MGD).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: June 15 - ID: "A" - Negs 2 thru 19 are various shots of the cache sites and extracted supplies on top of the ground. All of the shots are of weapons - no rice. Negs 32 and 33: Hook working out of Shakey's Hill.
- Contact Sheet 16425, 1970 June 15
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Cambodia - "B" operations negatives - Cambodian operations - partial scan (MGD).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: "B" neg is sign that reads "Welcome to Shakey's Hill." Negs 3 and 4: Walking along a jungle trail with grunts. Negs 5: Grunt with VC claymore mines. Negs 6 and 7: The chow line. Negs 9 and 10: Unloading Huey, or Slick, at Shakey's. These are also termed long birds (for logistics). Neg 16: Grunts returning from the field. Neg 17: A 105mm howitzer firing. Neg 18 and 19: Looking forward over the jungle. Neg 20 and 21: A cache being blown up - smoke mushrooming. Negs 22, 23, and 24: General scenes of Shakey's. Negs 26 thru 31: Shots from the C&C ship (Command and Control). I think the best might be 28. The others look a bit rough.
- Contact Sheet 16426, 1970 June 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Lt. Col. Kenneth A. Howard - officers - June 11, 1970.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pacific - June 11 - ID for Howard photos - All pictures in negative holder marked "Howard" are of Lt Col. Kenneth A. Howard.
- Contact Sheet 16427, 1970 June 27
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Vietnamese - political defectors.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Photo IDs - NVA defectors - Frames 26 and 27: Tran Van Mai. Frames 29 and 30: Tran Van Tinh.
- Contact Sheet 16448, 1970 June 13
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - girls - Sherri Nicholls - no.3.
- Contact Sheet 16449, 1970 June 13
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - girls - Sherri Nicholls - no.2.
- Contact Sheet 16450, 1970 December 4
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for cheesecake pix - Apr. 12, 70 - Hirst - Eric: All pix are of Miss Sherri Nicholls, a 19-year-old dancer with the "Revue 70" show currently making the military circuit in Vietnam. It's my first experiment with cheesecake, but possibly there is a shot or two in the series worthy of either a back page or something in the way of cheesecake inside the paper. Sherri hails from Sydney, Australia and this is her first trip to 'Nam. "I think the guys here are just super," says Sherri. By the way, I know you're terribly busy, but I'd certainly appreciate any tips on how to shoot better cheesecake pix. Posing attractive girls is a bit different from taking combat flicks. One final thought: That was a helluva fine layout you did in the March 21st issue with my pix from Hill 474. Cheers, Don Hirst.
- Contact Sheet 16452, 1970 May 18
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sp4 Herman E. Shows - crimes - acquittal - S. Sgt. Edgar Davidson - Shows trial.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: May 18 - Identification for Shows story - Frame 1: Sp4 Herman E. Shows who was acquitted of attempted murder charge. Frame 3-7: S Sgt Edgar Davidson who was injured in the grenade attack. Frames 9 to 11: From left to right Mike Creel, Shows' neighbor from home. Sp4 Herman E. Shows, his father Herman L. Shows, and Sin Cooley, Show' football coach.
- Contact Sheet 16453, 1970 May 14
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - traffic accident - Sgt. Chales B. Charlton - Pvt. Nguyen Van Phuoc - Charlton court.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pacific - May 14 - ID for Charlton court pix - Pictures--Charlton negligent homicide. Frames 2 & 3: Sgt Charles P. Charlton who was convicted negligent homicide in killing an ARVN MP. Frames 4-5-6: Key prosecution witness Pvt Phuoc.
- Contact Sheet 16454, 1970 July 4
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - soldiers - individuals.
- Contact Sheet 16455, 1970 May 18
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - O.W.sports, May 18, 1970 - Greg Smith - Mike Riordan - man on street (hijack worries), July 26, 1970.
- Contact Sheet 16456, 1970 July 9
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sp4 L. V. Allen - shooting - Allen trial.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pacific - July 9 - ID for negative attached: for Allen trial - Frame no. 6: Sp4 L. V. Allen is black man, in hat, coming out door. Man in right foreground.
- Contact Sheet 16457, 1970 July 2
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sfc. Hubert L. Anderson - Capt. Matt Lees - theft - acquittal.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for unsouped roll of tri-x containing art for Anderson trial - July 2, 70 - Hirst - It contains pix of Anderson (left) and his lawyer, Capt. Matt Lees (right) after the charges were dismissed.
- Contact Sheet 16458, 1970 May 9
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Maj. Delbert W. Fleener - Narcotics - offices - George Latimer - Capt. William Willis - May 9 and May 23, 1970.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs Pacific - Art for Fleener trial; Latimer interview - Identification of pictures for the Fleener Trial. First five frames: Pix of Capt Mandelstam for story I'm holding and may send in. Following frames, in order, showing man in civilian clothes: Maj Delbert W. Fleener's civilian attorney, George Latimer of Salt Lake City, Utah. Frames showing man in military uniform: Fleener's assigned defense counsel, Capt. William Willis. Rest of Frames: The boxes of opium Fleener was convicted of smuggling into Vietnam.
- Contact Sheet 16459, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sp4 Donald L. Roche - crimes - Capt. James Linebarger.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overs pacific - May 7 - ID for Roche trial negatives: Frame 2a: Defense lawyer Linebarger in front, Roche ducking behind him. Frame 3a: Defense Lawyer Capt. James Linebarger in foreground; Sp4 Ronald L. Roche behind him.
- Contact Sheet 16461, 1970 May 14
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - prisons - US Army - LBJ - Long Binh Jail - no. 1.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for Long Binh jail story - May 14, 70 - Frames 1, 2: Sign at right says "USARV Correctional Holding detachment." Frames 6, 7 show gate to the Long Binh jail. Frame 8: Guard tower and part of fence at stockade. Frame 3: more pix of sign. 4, 5: More shots of LBJ guard towers. Note screening material that covers lower half of fence--prevents anyone from looking in--or out.
- Contact Sheet 16464, 1970 July 1
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Okinawa - night life - Koza night life - no. 2.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet two for Koza nightlife - July 1, 70 - Hirst - Frames 1-3: B.C. street after dark. 4: Typical whores who inhabit Suckahotchie Alley. 5: Koza Bargirls. 6: Picture outside Koza nightclub advertising strip show. 7-18 show a round-eyed stripper doing her thing. These were shot at extremely low speed, I'm afraid, so there's a bit of a blurr. 19-22: Shows the same stripper acting as customer bait outside another club. 22-23: More shots of a a stripper, this time an Okinawan girl who takes it all off. 26: Another shot of B.C. Street. 27-30 are bar girls. 31: A Suckahotchie Alley joygirl.
- Contact Sheet 16466, 1970 June 18
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Korea (statue of MacArthur) - battlefild - Korea.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Oseas pacifik - Battlefield / Korean series - June 18 - Procter - Art IDs - Negs 1 thru 8 are of the statue of MacArthur at Inchon. Negs 12, 13, 14, 15 and 17: Overlooking sandy beach near landing site. Negs 19 and 20: A commemorative monument. Neg 20a is a shot of a jetty, fishing boats in foreground and island of Wolmi-do in background.
- Contact Sheet 16467, 1970 June 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Panmunjom art "A" - Korea.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: June 29 - Proctor - "A" Neg 1: Looking into a tower on Freedom House. Neg 2: American MPs stand around in Joint Security area, Panmunjom. Neg 3: A Swiss general raps with American (from neutral nations supervisory team). Neg 4: Col Han arriving. Neg 5: Swiss general puffs pipe (same as above general). Neg 6: The secretaries meeting starts, Col Jessup left, Han right. Neg 7: Swiss general (again!) rapping with Czech general. Neg 8: Korean newsman hanging around. Neg 9: MP and Red guard. Neg 10 and 11 is another of the conference table. Neg 12 and 13: Looking over the demarcation line into North Korea. Negs 14 and 15: The Bridge of No Return, with plains of North Korea in background. Neg 16: telephoto of Han (looking straight at camera). Negs 17, 18 and 19: Telephotos of Jessup. Neg 20: Another shot of Han.
- Contact Sheet 16468, 1970 July 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Panmunjom art "B" - Korea.